export const categoryArr = 
[
  { id: 1, category: "who said what"},
  { id: 2, category: "prophecies, dreams, miracles"},
  { id: 3, category: "minor prophets"},
  { id: 4, category: "kings of judah/israel"},
  { id: 5, category: "genealogy"},
  { id: 6, category: "fill in the blank"}
];

export const dollarValArr = 
[
  { id: 1, dollarVal: "200"},
  { id: 2, dollarVal: "400"},
  { id: 3, dollarVal: "600"},
  { id: 4, dollarVal: "800"},
  { id: 5, dollarVal: "1000"}
];

export const tableArr =
[  // 200 row
  { id: 1, 
    question: "'I am the light of the world'", 
    answer: "Jesus", 
    categoryId: 1, 
    dollarValId: 1
  },

  { id: 2, 
    question: "This person fulfilled a prophecy spoken by Deborah", 
    answer: "Jael", 
    categoryId: 2, 
    dollarValId: 1
  },

  { id: 3, 
    question: "Jehovah taught this prophet the extent of His mercy through a bottle-gourd plant", 
    answer: "Jonah", 
    categoryId: 3, 
    dollarValId: 1
  },

  { id: 4, 
    question: "This is how many stones David put in his pouch before killing Goliath", 
    answer: "5", 
    categoryId: 4, 
    dollarValId: 1
  },

  { id: 5, 
    question: "This person's mother was Rahab", 
    answer: "Boaz", 
    categoryId: 5, 
    dollarValId: 1 
  },

  { id: 6, 
    question: "Should the ___ say to the Potter: 'What are you making?' Or should your work say: 'He has no hands'? (Isaiah 45)", 
    answer: "clay", 
    categoryId: 6, 
    dollarValId: 1
  },

  // 400 row
  { id: 7, 
    question: "'We have believed and have come to know that you are the Holy One of God'", 
    answer: "Peter", 
    categoryId: 1, 
    dollarValId: 2 
  },

  { id: 8, 
    question: "Elijah said the following about which false god at Mount Carmel?: 'Perhaps he is deep in thought or he has gone to relieve himself'", 
    answer: "Baal", 
    categoryId: 2, 
    dollarValId: 2
  },

  { id: 9, 
    question: "This prophet's book is the last of the Hebrew Scriptures", 
    answer: "Malachi", 
    categoryId: 3, 
    dollarValId: 2
  },

  { id: 10, 
    question: "This person was the last earthly king in the Davidic line when Jerusalem was destroyed", 
    answer: "Zedekiah", 
    categoryId: 4, 
    dollarValId: 2
  },

  { id: 11, 
    question: "This person's father was Enoch, and has the longest lifespan of Bible record: 969 years", 
    answer: "Methuselah", 
    categoryId: 5, 
    dollarValId: 2
  },

  { id: 12, 
    question: "Preach the word; be at it urgently in favorable times and ___ times (2 Tim 4)", 
    answer: "difficult", 
    categoryId: 6, 
    dollarValId: 2
  },
              
  // 600 row
  { id: 13, 
    question: "'For all things I have the strength through the one who gives me power'", 
    answer: "Paul", 
    categoryId: 1, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  { id: 14, 
    question: "Jehovah brought lasting judgment on this man's house because 'his sons are cursing God, but he has not rebuked them'", 
    answer: "Eli", 
    categoryId: 2, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  { id: 15, 
    question: "Jehovah reassured this prophet that his judgment will come at the right time: 'It will without fail come true. It will not be late!'", 
    answer: "Habakkuk", 
    categoryId: 3, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  { id: 16, 
    question: "This king had the shortest reign (3 months and 10 days)", 
    answer: "Jehoiachin", 
    categoryId: 4, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  { id: 17, 
    question: "Asenath bore Joseph two sons. This was the brother of Manasseh", 
    answer: "Ephraim", 
    categoryId: 5, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  { id: 18, 
    question: "He gave his parents honey to eat, and 'did not tell them he had scraped [it] out of the carcass of a ___' (Judges 14)", 
    answer: "lion", 
    categoryId: 6, 
    dollarValId: 3 
  },

  // 800 row
  { id: 19, 
    question: "'Do not imagine that because you are in the king's household you are any more likely to escape than all the other Jews'", 
    answer: "Mordecai", 
    categoryId: 1, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  { id: 20, 
    question: "This person dreamt of 'the sun and the moon and 11 stars bowing down to [him]'", 
    answer: "Joseph", 
    categoryId: 2, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  { id: 21, 
    question: "Jehovah instructed this prophet to endure spousal infidelity, and his marriage reflected Jehovah's loyal love and forgiveness towards Israel", 
    answer: "Hosea", 
    categoryId: 3, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  { id: 22, 
    question: "These two kings have the same name, were brothers-in-law, and ruled at the same time", 
    answer: "Jehoram", 
    categoryId: 4, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  { id: 23, 
    question: "This person's name meant 'One Seizing the Heel; Supplanter', and his brother's name meant 'Hairy'", 
    answer: "Jacob", 
    categoryId: 5, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  { id: 24, 
    question: "All of you clothe yourselves with ___ toward one another. (1 Peter 5)", 
    answer: "humility", 
    categoryId: 6, 
    dollarValId: 4 
  },

  // 1000 row
  { id: 25, 
    question: "'Alas, O Sovereign Lord Jehovah! I do not know how to speak, for I am just a boy'", 
    answer: "Jeremiah", 
    categoryId: 1, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  },

  { id: 26, 
    question: "This is what the promised Seed was called, which means 'He Whose It Is; He To Whom It Belongs'", 
    answer: "Shiloh", 
    categoryId: 2, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  },

  { id: 27, 
    question: "This prophet may have been a great-great-grandson of King Hezekiah and a relative of King Josiah", 
    answer: "Zephaniah", 
    categoryId: 3, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  },

  { id: 28, 
    question: "This is approximately how old Josiah was when Zebidah gave birth to his second son, Jehoiakim (Insight book)",
    answer: "14", 
    categoryId: 4, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  },

  { id: 29, 
    question: "Two Jacobs in the Bible both had a son with this name", 
    answer: "Joseph", 
    categoryId: 5, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  },

  { id: 30, 
    question: "Abraham named that place ___. This is why it is still said today: 'In the mountain of Jehovah it will be provided.' (Gen 22)", 
    answer: "Jehovah-jireh", 
    categoryId: 6, 
    dollarValId: 5 
  }
];

export const teams = [
  {
    id: 1,
    questions: [
      { 
        questionId: 0,
        isCorrect: false,
        dollarVal: 0
      }
    ]
  }
];